Guide to the Montana State Prison records 1864-1974
Montana Historical Society
- Montana State Prison
  - Prisoner Records
    - Prisoner description cards: John Foley, Mike Foley, R.H. Foley, Thomas Foley, Thomas J. Foley, John Follows The Road, Louis Folsom, Robert Folster, Tom Fong, Wong Fong, Gerald Fontaine, Toy, Foo (Chinaman), Wong Foo, Edd Foote, Edward C. Foot, Florence Ford, Frank Ford, J.J. Ford, Joseph Clarence Ford, Nelson Ford, Oscar Ford, Patrick Ford, C.L. Forde, John Foreman, Reno Foreman, Jack Forester, George Forgey, Gordon Forlkstad, Joe Fornell, Raymond George Forrester, Charles Fors, Enoc Forse, Robert L. Forshee, Gilman Forsness, Frank F. Forster, William A. Forsyth, William Forsyth, Henry Fort, James Fortner, Howard G. Fortner (alias Sam F. Martin), Edward Fortune, Elmo Fortune, Joe Fortune, David Fose, Earl Foss, Olaf Melvin Fossum, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Prisoner description cards: Albert D. Foster, Charles Foster-True name is Jesse Merton, Chiles Eugene Foster, Donald Dean Foster, Edward Foster, Elwood Foster, Frank E. Foster, Frank Foster, Horace P. Foster, Junius Foster, Leander, Foster, Monroe Foster (alias C. Smith), Raymond Foster, Richard Foster, Russsell R. Foster, William Fountain, Fred Foucher, P.B. Fourtner, Leslie H. Fowler, Louis L. Fowler, Thomas Fowler, W.T. Fowler, Forrest Fowlkes, Arthur Fox, John A. Fox, Kenneth Fox, LeRoy Fox, Mike Fox, Theodore Fox, Thomas Earl Fox, William Fox, George Frach (alias Gordon Foulds), Thomas Frame, Thomas Frampton, Art Francis, Pete Francis, James Francis, Thomas Francis, Joe Franco, James H. Frank, Charles Franklin, Clifford Franklin, Dennis Franklin, Ernest Franklin, George Franklin, J.M. Franklin, Jack Franklin, James Franklin, James Willis Franklin, Deats Franklin, Thomas Franklin, Frank Franko, John Franks, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Prisoner description cards: Clarence J. Frary, Charles Fraser, Donald W. Fraser, Alex Frazier, Charles Frazier, Harold E. Frazier, Henry Frazier, George William Frederick, James K. Free, Ben Freeman, Clarence Freeman, Dewey Freeman, Dewey Freeman, Elmer E. Freeman, George Freeman, Randall J. Freeman, Spencer Freeman, Tommy J. Freeman, Don Freer, Henry Freestad, Ernest Freestone, George Freestone, Paul Freeze, Dudley French, Edgar French, Roy French, Virgil French, Frank Frenco, Lloyd Freng, Carlos Frentez, Frenzel J. Raymond, Cornelius Freseman, E.G. Freshwater, John Frey, John Frey, L.H. Frey, Harry Friberg, Roy Frickey, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Prisoner description cards: Henry Friedman, Jake Friezen, Leonard Raymond Frisbie, Jack Friske, Albert Fritsh, Adam Fritz, Dan Fritz, Floyd B. Fritz, C.D. Fritzen (Cleon Donald), Ray Fritzsom, Raymond Robert Frizzell, Carl Frodsham, Frank Frodsham, Frank Phylander Frodsham, Cecil Frost, Henri Froustey, Harvey H. Fry, Edwin C. Frye, Elvin Fuhrman, Thomas Fuji, Max Fukelman, Al Fuller (alias Harrison Kennedy), Elmer Fuller, Fred Franklin Fuller, George Fuller, J.R. Fuller, Ralph Fuller, Ralph J. Fuller, Ralph Fuller, Charles N. Fulmer, Louis Fundinger, Jim Fung, Ernest Funk, Joseph Frank Furlong, William Furnish, Joe C. Furst, Lewis Furstenau, L. Fustenau, Lewis James Furstenau, George Furthmeyer, Ira Fuson, Walter Fuson, Laurence Fust, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Prisoner description cards: Joe Gabanna, Paul Gabel, George Gable, David Gabrielson, Edward Charles Gaebe, Grover Gaffney, Leslie L. Gaffney, Thomas Gaffney, Shannon Gage, Matt Gaggio, E. Gagnier, Gust Gaimos, Lloyd C. Gaine, Clyde Gaines, Ellie Gaines, James E. Gaines, Max L. Gaines, Max Gaines, Jose Gaitan, Stewart Gakllaway, Arthur Galahan, Arthur H. Galahan, Leo J. Galahan, Ernest Galavig, Charles H. Gale, David Gale, Frank Gale, James Gale, James Morris Gale, Clarence Gallagher, H.N. Gallagher (alias H.M. Locke), James Gallagher, Vincent E. Gallagher, Carl J. Gallin, John Gallineau, Dave Gallo, Peter Gallucci, Robert Gallus, Charles Galvin, Allen G. Gamble, N.W. Gamble, Leland Clyde Gammon, Henry Ganier, Tony Ganni, Barney Gannon, Abraham Garcia, Alfred Garcia, Agistin Garcia, Charles Garcia, Domingo Garcia, Fausto Garcia (Informed against as Fausto Garcia Lopez), Felix Garcia, Frank Garcia, Fred Garcia, Joe Garcia, Jose M. Garcia, Jose V. Garcia, Juan Emanuel Garcia, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Prisoner description cards: Larry Garcia, Lewis Herman Garcia, Louis Garcia, Roy Garcia, Santos Garcia, Kenneth Gardiner, Ray Gardiner, A.P. Garding, Al Garding, Alphonse Garding, Alfred Gardipee, Henry Gardipee (Sometimes known as Little Blaze), John Gardipee, Louis Gardepe (Gardipee), Charles Gardner, Clifford Orley Gardiner, E.H. Gardner, Fred Gardner, Fred W. Gardner, Jack Gardner, John D. Gardner, Robert or Hobert Gardner, Ray Gardy, Albert Garier, James Garland, William Garland, Charles Garlock, Irving Garlock, Cessem Garner, Emmett Garner, Mable Garner, Otis Garner, Walter Garner, Walter Buck Garner, William Garner, Robert Garney, A.B. Garrett, Earl Garrett, Earl Garrett (alias James Mulligan), Omer Dennis Garrett, Utah Carl Garrett, Everett Garrick, Lewis B. Garrison, Roy Garroutte, Edward Garswick, John Garvey, Herman Gartro, Mike Garvey, Seward P. Garwood, Francis Gatecloux, A.J. Gates, Arthur L. Gates, L.C. Gatewood, Ben Gathany, Benjamin Gathany, Claud Gatliff, John Gaub, Gloria Gaudry, Victor Gaudry, Victor Gaudry (alias Victor Davis), Victor Gaudry (alias Vital Gaudry), Henry Gault, Orville Cauthier, Roger Gauthier, Frank Gavard, Philip Gavin, Reginald Gay, Steve Gaydash, Joseph Gaydos, Harry Gaylord, Alex Gaynor, G.W. Gazaway, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Prisoner description cards: Thomas Gearhart, Harold Gebhardt, Marvin Gee, Leonard Geesey, Ray Gehlen, Louis E. Geis, Charles M. Geller, Joe Gelsleichter, Henry Gendrow, Arthur Genereaux, Lawrence Genest, Homer L. Gennetti, Jacob Gensburg, Charles Gentle (alias Charles Riley), John George, Mike George, Nick George, Newney George, Paul George, Steve George, Woodrow George, Lawrence Gerald, Max Gerald, Ray Gerber, Lee Gerer, George W. Gerrick, A.C. Gess, Arthur Gess, Ernest Gertson, Albert Giadush, Joe Giardinello, Dominick Giarratana, Earl Arthur Gibbs, George Gibbs, Charles Gibson, Ed Gibson, George W. Gibson, John Gibson, Mike Gibson, Ottis F. Gibson, Robert Gibson, Tom Gibson, Delbert Leroy Giddens, George Gidenbach, George Giedd, Ed Gieske, Joe Gifford, Antanacio Gil, Calvin C. Gilbert, Dean Gilbert, Floyd Gilbert, M.L. Gilbert, Murry Gilbert, W.E. Gilbert, Henry gilbertson, Irene Gilchrist, John Gilchrist, I.A. Giles, Leewood Sidney Giles, Jack L. Giles, Lottie Giles, William Giles, Bernard Gilham, Bernard Gilham, Mike Gilhooley, Felix Gill, George Gill (alias Iden Green; Golden Green and Craig Kennedy), John Gill, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Prisoner description cards: Ethel Gillespie, George Francis Gillett, Clarence Hubberd Gillette, Donald Gillette, Donald E. Gillette, George Gillette, Harold Gillette, Walter H. Gillette (alias Walter Ward), Ray Gilley (alias George Taylor and Roy Kelley), Roy Gillian, W. Mayhew Gillies, Terrence Gilliland, William Gillon, Roy A. Gilman, Theodore Gilman, Vernon E. Gilmer, Alfred F. Gilmore (alias O'Malley; Larry; alias Larry Allen), Clarence Gilmore, George Gilmore, Harry L. Gilmore, Jack Gilmore, Tom L. Gilmore, Walter Gilmore, Alfred J. Gilroy, Frank Gilroy, Frank Gilstrap, Romeo Gingras, John Giovanetti, Lorenzo Giovannini, Orville Girard, Andre Giroux, Walter Giza, Iver Gjermore, Mike Gladeau, Tom Gladeau, Ray Gladue, William Glancy Jr., William J. Glancy, Thomas Glanton (alias Jeff Thompson), Arthur Glatt, Tony Glavinich, Orin R. Gleerup, James P. Gleeson, H.J. Glenn, Jim Glenn, Louis Glenn, Robert Glenn, Mike Glennon, Ralph Glidewell, George Glomski, John Gloski, Charles C. Glover, Henry Glover, Ben Glusac, Alex Glynn, Earl Raymond Glynn, Earl Glynn, Earl R. Glynn, Melville Anderson Glynn, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Prisoner description cards: Charles Goar, Charles A. Goar, George Goble Jr., Mike Gocni, Harry Goddard, Harold Godrrey, James George Godfrey, Gus Godley (alias Harry Jones), Bruce Godwin, James Hurst Godwin, Walter Godwin, Frank Goedert, A.L. Goer, Rufus Goer, Ronald R. Goerlich, Howard Goforth, John S. Goforth, John T. Goforth, Hayes Gogeles, Denny Goggin, Mike Goggin, Hayes Goggles, William Goings, Rodney Goins, Ben Gold, J.A. Goldberg, Herman Golden, Joe Gomeros, Robert Gomerson, Andrew Gomez, Arturo Gomez, Benjamin Gomez, Felix Gomez, Gilbert Gomez, Jesse Gomez, Joe Angel Gomez, Joe Gomez, Laurence Padilla Gonzales, Luis Gonzales, Marvin Gonzales, Pedro M. Gonzales, Pedro Gonzales, Ruben Gonzales, Robert W. Good, Roy Goodhal, Harry Goodland, Raphael Eugene Goodman, Wallace Goodrich, Jim Gopher, Harold Gordon, Harry L. Gordon, Ira Gordon, Thomas Edward Gordon, Joe Goretti, Thomas P. Gorey, Henry C. Gorham, Clarence Goss, Carl Gossett, John Gotham, Phil Goudry, Phillip Goudry, Jesse Clark Goulette, Blair Goyins, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Prisoner description cards: George Gondeiro, Joe Gonzalig, Mark Good, Lyle Goodchild, Jerry Goodin, John Goodman, Steve Goodrich, George Goodrow, James Goodwin (alias J.A. LaVolley), Jerry Goodwin, Philip Goodwin, William Goodyer, John F. Gordon, John T. Gordon, Louis Gordon, Wesley Gordon, William Gordon, Harry P. Gorman, James Gorman (True Name is Harry Drummond), Louis Gorman, Harry Gosney, Silas Goss, Fred Gould, Ira Gould, Thomas Gould, Willard Gould, Alfred Gould, William Gough, Gottlieb Grabatin, Frank Grace, Harry Grady, James A. Grady, George Graff, Lauren Graff, Lewis A. Graff, Martin Graff, Charles R. Graham, Charles W. Graham, George Graham, Harold Graham, John Graham, John Graham, L.J. Graham, Milton Graham, Smokey Graham, Milford Grainger, Stanley Grams, Ernest Granbois, Robert Granbois, Robert Granbois, Roy Granby, Harry W. Grandon, John Grandovic, Robert Gransberry, Robert Grandsbury, Robert Gransberry, Robert Gransbury, Robert L. Grandstaff, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Prisoner description cards: Robert Graney, Carl Granger, Alexander Grant, Cecil Grant, Charles L. Grant, Charles M. Grant, Daniel Paul Grant, Eugene Grant, Fred Grant, J.V. Grant, Robert Grant, Martin Grasswick, Douglas John Gravelle, Martin Gravelle, Ray R. Gravelle, Joe Graves, John Graves, John Paul Graves, Leslie Leroy Graves, Alexander Gray, Bruce Gray, C.T. Gray, Elton Gray, Fred Gray (alias Joe Brennan, Gabe Gray, Herbert Gray, J.D. Gray, James Gray, Morris Gray, Oliver T. Gray, Raymond Gray, Ronald W. Gray, S.C. Gray, Tom Gray, Joe Grebenc, Charles Green, Charlie Green, Donald Green, Donald S. Green, Earl Green, Frederick Carl Green, Gradon Green, Harry Green, Irwin Green, Jack W.L. Green, Leard E. Green, Marion Green, Richard Green, Robert Green, Roy Green, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Prisoner description cards: Sam Green, Sidney Green, William Green, Fred Greenbeck, Harry Greene, Lawrence John Greene, Raymond P. Greene, William Greenfield, Gerald Greeno, Price Greenup, Roy Greenup, Woody Greenwell, B.A. Greer, J.G. Greer, G.L. Gregory, Guy Gregory, Johnnie Mack Gregory, Mark A. Gregory, William M. Gregory, LeRoy Grenier, Steve Gresh, William Charles Grey, Thomas Grey (alias Tom Allen), Tom Grey, Thomas Grey, Fred Warren Grey, Robert Grey, Stewart Grey, Nicholas J. Gribnau, Herbert Grice, George Griego, Thomas Griff, Bennett Griffin, Edward Griffin, Ed Griffin, Francis Griffin, George Griffin, Harry Griffin, James W. Griffin, Jim Griffin, John Griffin, John W. Griffin, Louis Griffin, Nathaniel Griffin, Robert J. Griffin, Richard R. Griffin, Thomas Griffin, William Griffin, Frank Griffis, B.F. Griffith, J.A. Griffith, William B. Griffith, Thornton A. Griggs, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Prisoner description cards: James R. Grimes, John Grimes, Irene Grimm, Walter Grimm, Millard Grimmett, J.B. Grimsley, Robert Franklin Grimsley, Floyd Joseph Grina, James Grinder, Jim Grinder, Jose Grine, Gus Grinsteiner, Joseph Grinstine, Pasquale Grisolia, B.L. Griswold, Charles L. Griswold, Charles L. Griswold, Earl H. Grswold, Malcolm Griswold, Joe Grivel, William Grogan, Lynn Groom, Thomas Groom, L.E. Grooms, Walter Grooms, Jacob Groscop, Ben Gross, Ben F. Gross, J.P. Gross, John Grossman, Albert J. Grosso, Paul Grosswiler, Henry Grotbo (alias Roy Garroutte), Henry Grotbo (alias Roy Garroutte), Norman Grothe, Edward Grotjan, Jack Grove, Alvin Grover, George Grovert, Gus Grovert, Walter Donald Groves, Earl Grow, Thurston Grow, Albert Grube, Harold Albert Grube (alias Harold Vollrath), 1910-1955 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Prisoner description cards: Augustin Guardiola, Christy P. Guardipee, Coleman Guardipee, Wilson J. Guardipee, Harold Eugene Guenzler, David Guerra, Clarence Guest, Fred Guevara, Jack Guider, Ernest Guidette, Alphonse Guie, Lee Guiear, Andrea Guigni, Joseph Welmer Guinn, Robert Gumerson, Walter Gumm, Earl R. Gummer, Earl Gummer, J.M. Gump, Stephen Gundario, Glenden Gunderson, John Gunderson, Robert Gunderson, Frank Gunn, Mamie Gurney, Peter Guss, Earnest R. Gust, Louis Gust, Frank Gustin, Jesus Guterrez, Nick Calder Guterrez, Lawrence Guthrie, Gulermo Gutierez, Joe Gutierz, Arthur William Gutknecht, Donald Raymond Guyer, Harlan Guynn, Harlian Guynn, Thomas Gwynn, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Prisoner description cards: Charley Haabala, E.E. Haag, Grace Haagenson, Arnold Haaland, Clem Haas, Howard Raymond Haas, Oscar Haase, Oscar Haase, Victor Hackala, Harry Hackett, Joseph Hackl, Albert Haddock, Haderli A. Edwin, Aarron Hadwyn, Richard Haessly, Charles Haffeman, Charles A. Haffeman, James Hagan, John Hagan, John Hagan, William Hagan, George Hagberg, Nels Hageland, A.C. Hagen, Roy Hagen, William Hagen, William B. Hagewood, Gerald P. Haggerty, Leo Hagins, Y. Hagiwara, Edward H. Hahn, John Hails, H.J. Haines, Jimmy Haines, Jacob O. Hakala, Eddie Halcomb, John Hale, William Hale, Wallace Hale, William Hale, William F. Hale, Herbert W. Hales, Jack Haley, Thomas P. Haley, George E. Halfacre, Frank Halferty, Albert F. Halk, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Prisoner description cards: Art Hall, Charles Hall, Clinton Hall, Denver Hall, Ed Hall, Edwin V. Hall, Frank Hall, Frank C. Hall, Fred D. Hall, George Hall, Grundy Hall, Harry Hall, Jake Hall, James E. Hall, Jesse Hall, John Hall, John Allen Hall, Leslie Hall, Lewis Hall, Martin Hall, Mitchell Hall, Sam A. Hall, Viber Hall, W.D. Hall, W.W. Hall, William Hall, Charles Harry Hallam, Celcil Hallford, Emil Hallin, James Henry Hallock, Gus Halonen, Uno Halstrom, Ola Halverson, Warren Stuart Halverson, Reidar Halvorsen, Arthur Hambidge, Alfred Hamel, Raymond Hamel, Walter Hamelan, Dave C. Hamiton, Edwin Grant Hamlton, Herman Hamilton, James Hamilton, John A. Hamilton, Leonard Hamilton, Robert Hamilton, Robert Waldo Hamilton, Thomas H. Hamilton, William Albert Hamilton, William H. Hamilton, Woodrow Hamilton, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Prisoner description cards: Floyd Hamlin, Harold Hamlin, George Hamm, William Hammea, Lewis Christopher Hammel, Lewis Hammel, Lewis C. Hammel, Ralph Hammell, Charles Hammer, Clarence Hammer, Clarence Hammer, Sam Hammett, Charles Hammick, Charles R. Hammick, Ed Hammond, Emanuel Hammond, Guy Hammond, H.O. Hammond, Arden Andy Hammons, Harry Hampson, Oscar L. Hampton, Wade Hampton, John Hanberg, Albert Hanbrich, George E. Hanchett, Arthur W. Hancock, M.T. Hand, John Handley, John L. Handley, Roy Handran, Walter Handy, Rex Arlington Haneline, Lester Haney, Joe Haney, James Haniafain, Frank M. Hankin, Pierre Hanks, R.F. Hanks, Walter E. Hanks, Charles Hanley, Edward Hanley, Ed Hanley, Jack Hanley, Michael J. Hanley, S.L. Hanley, Guy C. Hanna, W.G. Hanna, David Hannah, Russ Hannah, Frank Hanneck, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Prisoner description cards: Joe Hannon, Chris Hansen, Frederick Lone Hansen, Helmer Hansen, John Hansen, Julius Hansen, Julius M. Hansen, Magnon Hansen, Alton Hanson, Clarence Albert Hanson, Earl B. Hanson, Gale Hanson, George Albert Hanson, George J. Hanson, Marvin H. Hanson, Hans C. Hanson, Harold S. Hanson, Henry Hanson, Henry H. Hanson, Herman Hanson, Jack Hanson, Lowell A. Hanson, M.F. Hanson, Magnus Hanson, Magnus Ferdinand Hanson, Myron Hanson, Ole Hanson, Ray Hanson, Henry Hanzenbach, Harry B. Happy, Arnold Harala, I.W. Harbert, George Harbour, George Harcharick, Lloyd Harden, Ralph Hardenbrook, Harold Hardin, Ed Harding, Frederick Harding, Frederick W. Harding, Lloyd Harding, D.R. Hardincourt, Charles Hardy, William Hardy, Rutledge Hargrove, T.J. Hargrove, Henry Harig, Ed Harkins Sr., James G. Harkins, W.H. Harlow, Alfred Harmon, Edward Harmon, John Harmon, Thomas Harmon, Vern Harmon, Nelo Haro, D.C. Harper, Carl Oma Harrell, Claude Harrell, Arthur Harrington, Cleo Harrington, D.S. Harrington, Earl Harrington, Ed Harrington, Emmett Harrington, Herbert Harrington, John Harrington, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Prisoner description cards: B.O.P. Harris, Bertram Harris, Bob Harris, Charles Harris, Charles E. Harris, Charles Leroy Harris, Clark Harris, D.H. Harris, Donald A. Harris, E.O. Harris, Francis H. Harris, Frank Harris, Frank F. Harris, George Harris, Henry Harris, J.B. Harris, Jack Harris, Jack D. Harris, Jim Harris, Joe Harris, Joseph Harris, Joseph H. Harris, Joseph Harold Harris, L.H. Harris, Monte Harris, Paul A. Harris, Peter Alvin Harris, Richard Harris, William Harris, William Edward Harris, William P. Harris, Wilson A. Harris, Frank Harrison, Fred J. Harrison, Fred Harrison, George A. Harrison, Lee Harrison, Lynn Harrison, Roy Harrison, Starling Reibel Harrison, W.E. Harrison, William Harrison, James Harry, Fred Harsha, Kenneth Harstad, Claude Hart, Donald Hart, F.P. Hart, Glenn L. Hart, James Hart, J.W. Hart, John Hart, Joseph Hart, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Prisoner description cards: Leo Charles Hart, Tex Hart, Thomas Hart, William Hart, Fred Harter, Chester Hartford, Vernest Hartford, William Hartford, Ralph Harthouse, Roy Hartlett, Howard Hartley, Charles Hartman, Cupid Hartman (alias Stella Harvey), George Hartman, William Hartman, Fred Hartness, John A. Hartry, Harry Hartsell, R.E. Hartsough, Harry Hartung, M.H. Hartung, J.J. Hartwell, J.C. Hartzell, Bernard L. Harvey, Dave Harvey, E.H. Harvey, George Harvey, Harry Harvey, James Harvey, John Harvey, Leo Harvey, William Harvey, Fred Harvill, Frank Harwell, Joe Harwood, Glen Hash, John Hashek, Fay S. Haskins, Fay Haskins, Thomas W. Haskins, Thomas Haskins (alias Tony Long and James Green), Orland Benjamin Hassan, Oscar Hasse, T.E. Hassett, Charles Hatcher, Leo Hatcher, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Prisoner description cards: Carl Hatfield, Charles D. Hatfield, Harry E. Hatfield, Donald C. Hathaway, George E. Hatten, James Hatton, George H. Hatzenbuehler, Albert Haubrich, Kenneth Haugan, Morris Haugen, Oscar Haugen, Elton Haughey, Anthony J. Hauptmann, Vern Hauserman, John C. Havard, Ed Havensm, George Harvely, Howard Clark Haverman, James Hawe, Jules Hawgyt, Ben Jay Hawk, David Hawkes, James V. Hawkes, Aster H. Hawkins, Delmar Hawkins, Herman E. Hawkins, Jack Hawkins, John Hawkins, William E. Hawkins, Frank Hawley, George Edward Haworth, Sidney M. Hawver, Chung Hay, Donald Robert Hay, John Hay, Clinton Hayes, George Hayes, H.E. Hayes, J.B. Hayes, Louis Hayes, R.J. Hayes, Richard Hayes, Thomas D. Hayes, Bartle Hayfield, John Hayfield, Frank Haynes, Marlowe K. Haynes, G.H. Hays, Marce Hays, William H. Hays, Clarence B. Hayward, Glen Hazelwood, James R. Hazen, Willaim Hazen, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Prisoner description cards: Stole Head Carrier, A.J. Heagy, Ernest Healy, R.H. Heane, Kenneth E. Heard, William Hearsey, William J. Heaston, Hannah Heath, Paul Heath, R.F. Heath, Joe Heather, Sam Heatherly, Myron Louis Heavlin, Richard Heavygun, Adam Heberlein, William Heckenberg, John R. Hedberg, Mae Hedge, Reuben Hedger, Chauncet A. Hedges, Marx Hedgpeth, Henry C. Hedrick, William A. Hedrick, Edith Heffelfinger, Norman L. Hefferlfinger, Ernest Hegman, Ted Heide, Archie Heim, E.D. Heimstreet, Albert Heinbaugh, Boyd Heinbaugh, Boyd Heinbaugh, W.H. Heinze, Norman Heise, Jewell Heiser, Theodore Francis Heisler, Forest Helfer, Gilmore Helgeland, Eugene A. Heigeson, Eugene Arnold Helgeson, Ed Hellos, James Owen Helm, Louis Helm, Mellard Helman, Richard Helten, Ray Helvey, Herman J. Helwich, Melvin G. Helwich, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Prisoner description cards: Tom Hem, W.L. Hemrick, Huie Hen, A.M. Henderson, Glen W. Henderson, Henry Henderson, James Henderson, Jack Henderson, Frank Henderson, John Henderson, Peter Henderson, Thomas Henderson, Wilford Henderson, William Henderson, John Hendricks, Pete Hendricksmeir, Albert Henrickson, Harry Hendrickson, John Hendrickson, Richard L. Hendrickson, Roy Hendrickson, Thomas Hendrickson, Marvin Hendrix, Joseph L. Hendry, T.J. Henly, Grover E. Hennefield, Henry Henninger, Churchill Henry, George Henry, George Ray Henry, Jacob H. Henry, Joseph Edward Henry, L.B. Henry, Less Henry, Joseph Hensel, Carl Hensley, Joseph B. Herlihy, Kazumieur Herluzeka (alias Jim Miller), Walter Herman, Raymond Hermandez, William C. Hermann, Pete Hermansen (alias James Erickson), Augustine Hernandez, Hilario Hernandez, Joe Hernandez, Jose Hernandez, Tony Hernandez, Emigeleo Herrera, Luis Herrera, Antonio Herrero, Carroll E. Herrick, Charles Herrick, Leslie Herrin, Alan H. Herring, Joseph A. Herring, Glenn Herron, Jack P. Herron, William Hersha, William Hervert, Junior Pete Herzet, Ed Hess, Frank Hess, Henry Hess, Roy Hevener, Chester K. Hewitt, Emery Hewitt, Frederick Heyerdahl, B.C. Heykes, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Prisoner description cards: George Hibben, John W.A. Hicken, Mack Hickeson, George Hickey, Jack Hickey, James Hickey, Jerry Hickey, Charles Hickie, John W. Hicklin, Millard Hickman, Frank Hicks, Oscar Hicks, Walter Hicks, Vernon Hickson, John Hiebert, Havlor Higden, Earl Higginbotham, Herman B. Higgins, Robert Higgins, William A. High, Isaac Highland, Willie Hightower, Perfecto Higuera, Jesse Hildebran, Charles Hildermann, Aaron Hill, Charles Hill, C.O. Hill, Daniel Hill, Dixon Hill, Ed Hill, Emmett J. Hill, Frank Hill, George Hill, Gordon Alvin Hill, Guy Hill, Howard T. Hill, James Hill, James C. Hill, John E.Hill, Joe Hill, John Hill, John Wesley Hill, Lawrence Hill, Leon Hill, Melbourne M. Hill, Oscar Hill, Robert Hill, Rudolph Robert Hill, Thomas Franklin Hill, W.E. Hill, Willard B. Hill, William Hill, Horace Glen Hills, Romeo Romalice Hills, Clyde Hilton, E.F. Hilton, Chung Hin, Elmer Hinchey, Albert Hinchman, Mandus Hinderager, Alfred Tomkins Hindley, Charles Hines, Robert John Hines, Charlie Hing, Mah Sam Hing, Tom Hing, Archie Hinkle, David William Hinkle, Frank Hinkle, Catherine Hinkley, Henry Hinkley, Henry E. Hinkley, James Hinkle, Edgar George Hinman, Elmer Hinton, Walter Hinze, Gus Hirclay, James E. Hirst, William Hissong, Leo Hittle, Eugene Hively, Charles Hixon, H.J. Hixon, Guy LeRoy Hixson, 1910-1955 (Box-folder 20/3)